Finding Aid to the Alan Guttmacher Institute records SSC.MS.00720
Sophia Smith Collection
- Guttmacher Institute research files, staff files and project records, 2018-S-0052; 7.5 linear feet (6 record cartons)
  - 5 Year Plan files, 58 folders (58 folders)
    From the inventory sheet: "It is a bit difficult to pin down exactly which projects these files relate to. Many of the files relate to Title X and subsequent litigation. Some of the files relate to a project "Five Year Plan Family Planning Study." The dates of the files in these two boxes seem to range from the 1970s through the late 1980s."
    "Five Year Plan Family Planning Study" refers to multiple projects conducted for various organizations by the Guttmacher Institute, all iterations of the same core idea to study family planning through various lenses.
    - "Pop 81" population statistics and notes on race, poverty distribution, marital status, and income, plus programming information, 1980-1981; 6 folders (6 folders) (Box 5)
    - FY 1971 city and county study of family planning services and patterns (includes proposals, negotiations, questionnaires, study materials) (Box 5)
      From the questionnaire cover sheet: "This national survey is one part of a larger study which has been designed to: (a) estimate the number of women in need of subsidized family planning care and the number who received subsidized medical family planning services in fiscal year (FY) 1971; (b) identify the existing and potential resources for provision of family planning services; and (c) analyze the manpower utilization patterns of agencies which provide family planning services." The survey was conducted by the Guttmacher Institute in cooperation with the Council on Population of the American Public Health Association, the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, the American Hospital Association and the Association of State and Territorial Health Officers.
    - Family planning-related articles and reviews (including material by Joy G. Dryfoos), 1976-1980; 4 folders (4 folders) (Box 5)
    - Planned Parenthood court documents and relevant state bills, 1978-1986; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Guttmacher Title X background, memos, correspondence, and legal information, 1987-1991; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - NICHD (National Institute of Child Health and Human Development) family planning five-year plan evaluation and progress report, 1980-1981; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - DHHS (Department of Health and Human Services) family planning five-year plan contract, progress reports, methods, statistics, data, and analysis, 1980-1982; 15 folders (15 folders) (Box 6)
    - DHEW (Department of Health, Education, and Welfare) family planning five-year plan contracts, progress reports, relevant literature, technical proposals, and correspondence, 1976-1980; 7 folders (7 folders) (Box 6)
    - NCHS (National Center for Health Statistics) five-year plan proposal and budget, 1975; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Original inventory sheets, 2018; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 1)
- Alan Guttmacher Institute website, First captured 2015; 2013-S-0076; 1 website (1 website)
  The Institute publishes on its website a wide range of resources on topics pertaining to sexual and reproductive health, and articles from its two publishes two peer-reviewed journals, Perspectives on Sexual and Reproductive Health and International Perspectives on Sexual and Reproductive Health, and the public policy journal Guttmacher Policy Review. This archived website was first captured in October 2015. Subsequent captures are scheduled annually.
  - Guttmacher Institute Youtube channel, First captured June 29, 2018; 1 website (single)
    The archived YouTube channel of the Guttmacher Institute (https://www.youtube.com/user/Guttmacher/) was first captured in June 2018. Subsequent captures are scheduled.
- Alan Guttmacher Institute records, 1960-2013; 2013-S-0064
  This series contains the papers recieved from the Guttmacher institute in 2013. This includes reports, data, publications, projects, books, administrative and financial records, and correspondence from the years 1960 to 2013.
  Notable sections of the series include boxes 2-4, which contain the comprehensive records of the Maternal and Child Health Bureau (MCHB). Box 5 contains records of President Alan Guttmacher's correspondences and material related to his 1974 memorial service. The following two boxes, 6-7, offer comprehensive finanical paperwork, such as audits from 1982-1994 and endowment records. Boxes 11 and 12 contain records related to teenage fertility domestically and internationally, as well as doctor's/private physician surverys. The following box, 13, contains records related to AGI's grant from the Rockefeller Foundation. The bulk of the remaining seven boxes contain various publications from the AGI's journals and other publications related to sexual and reproductive health, both domestically and internationally.
  Arrangement
  The series remains arranged in the order that the donor sent it in to the SSC.
  - SDI Funding, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Risk/Benefit Using Ortho Data, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Risk/Benefit Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Risk/Benefit Draft Article, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Risk/Benefit Chartbook, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Risk/ Benefit Drafts, data notes etc, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Cost/Benefit California notes and report/ analysis, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Cost/Benefit California Background Work Notes, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Cost/Benefit California Proposals, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Cost/Benefit Analysis of Family Planning Expenditures - Henshaw/Chamie arctile, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Binder 1: Project Budgets grant information and reports, correspondence, project schedules and task lists., undated (Box 1)
  - Binder 2: Institute Budgets Salaries, institute spending, undated (Box 1)
  - Binder 3:Spending summary report annual for 1999, 2000, 2001, undated (Box 1)
  - Binder 4: Spending summary reports 1992, 1993, 1994, 1995, 1996, undated (Box 1)
  - Binder 5: Financial reports 2002, 2003, 2004, undated (Box 1)
  - Risk Benefit Proposal, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Cost/Benefit Misc, undated (Box 2)
  - PPFA Access Memos and Report, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Family Guide for Healthcare during pregnancy booklet, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Maternal and Child Health Bureau (MCHB), undated (Box 2)
  - MCHB Susheela Singh Project notes and baby book, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Baby your Baby Keepsake booklet, 1990 (Box 2)
  - MCHB budget, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Letters to NACHO and local health officials, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Memos, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Susheela's Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB County Study Tables, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB National Advisory, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Hospital Birth Certificate Records, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Misc, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Statistical Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Letter to Providers, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Research Evaluating Handbooks, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - CDC Meeting on Statistical Methods for Evaluation of interventions, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Handbook Appendices, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Correspondences Feds, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Donner and Other Statistical Pages re MCHB Project, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Don Martin Papers from CDC Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB work assignments, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB general articles on children, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB correspondence with NY department of health, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Utah notes, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Utah correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Utah, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Handbook trial materials, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Second Draft of Handbook and Comments, 1991 (Box 2)
  - MCHB Sample selection, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB questionnaires trail 1 and 2 in Spanish and English, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Final report, undated (Box 3)
  - MCHB First draft of Utah report, undated (Box 3)
  - MCHB Related publications, undated (Box 3)
  - MCHB Maryland Handbook initiative, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Provider panel meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB IRB materials, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB National advisory panel, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Birth Centers, 1991 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Medicaid directors, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB County selection, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Provider pane, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB National advisory panel, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Science advisory panel, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Multi-media, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB American academy of pediatrics, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Handbook follow up, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Sample Handbooks: Japan, Denver etc, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Handbook evaluation August- 1991Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Handbook evaluation April 1991-May 1991 Correspondence, Monthly Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - MCHB Handbook evaluation February-March 1991 Correspondence, Monthly Notes (Box 3)
  - MCHB Evaluation December, 1990 -January 1991 Correspondence, monthly notes etc, 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Abortion Politics by Jaffe Lindheim Lee, undated (Box 4)
  - Babies by Choice or by Chance by Alan F. Guttmacher, M.D., 1981 (Box 4)
  - Birth Control and Love (2) by Alan F. Guttmacher M.D. w. Winfield Best and Frederick S. Jaffe, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Family Planning Public Policy and Intervention Strategy by Frederick S. Jaffe, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Impact of Family Planning Programs in Fertility (2) by Phillip Cutrighy and Frederick S. Jaffe, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Libro Completo del Control de la Natalided by Alan F. Guttmacher M.D. w/ Winfield Best and Frederick S. Jaffe, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Planning Your Family Alan F. Guttmacher M.D. w/ Winfield Best and Frederick S. Jaffe, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Reproduction and Human Welfare (2) by Roy O. Greep, Marjorie A. Koblinsky and Frederick S. Jaffe, 1976 (Box 4)
  - A Complete Book of Birth Control (2) by Alan F. Guttmacher M.D. w/ Winfield Best and Frederick S. Jaffe, 1961 (Box 4)
  - The Consumers Union Report on Family Planning by Alan F. Guttmacher1962 (Box 4)
  - The Time Has Come- a Catholic doctor's proposals to end the battle over birth control by John Rock, M.D. w/ a forward by Christian A. Herter, 1963 (Box 4)
  - Letters from Alan F. Guttmacher to PPFA Supporters and Book proposal by Albert Altcheck M.D. on Alan Guttmacher 1974, undated (Box 5)
  - Stan Weed Publications, undated (Box 5)
  - Jane Murrary Publications, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Alan F Guttmacher M.D. Memorial Service 1974: tributes, service details, thank-yous, undated (Box 5)
  - Guttmacher Publications Support Materials and PPFA, undated (Box 5)
  - AGI National Conference on the Delivery of Family Planning Services in Rural America October 5-7 1977, undated (Box 5)
  - Alan F Guttmacher Centennial, 1998 (Box 5)
  - AGI gerneral description and important legal, financial, etc. information, 1991-2000 (Box 5)
  - Data Confidentiality, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Hayes report to the Ford Foundation re management issues, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Endowment Analysis, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Human Resources management report by Church and Shmavonian, 2000 (Box 5)
  - For-profit subsidiary analysis, 1990 (Box 5)
  - AGI Use/ AGI Citations by Anti-abortion groups WHO, CDC, undated (Box 5)
  - Anti-abortion use of AGI, undated (Box 5)
  - Batella Estimates of US Homosexuality 1993 Published in FPP, 1977 (Box 5)
  - Board Affairs: info on retreats, Board structure, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - Conflict of Interest; money from contraceptive manufacturers, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Indiana subpoena re.18 hour delay case, 1999 (Box 5)
  - International Planned Parenthood Affiliation Agreement, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Legal Assistance, 1995-1999 (Box 5)
  - Maternal and Child health correspondence re defunding by MCHB, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Partners Project: workshop on teen repro health, 1998 (Box 5)
  - PPFA/AGI Agreements: affiliation agreement, research track, 1977 (Box 5)
  - United Kingdom Social Exclusion analysis of teen pregnancy in the US, 1998 (Box 5)
  - United Nations, AGI role at UN meetings, 2001 (Box 5)
  - AGI Website early documents on design & function of site, 1996-1998 (Box 5)
  - Wisconsin case (Karlin v. Faust) subpoena, correspondences, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Buffet Letter 1987 (Box 5)
  - Frederick S Jaffee Memorial documents, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Guttmacher swag, 2012-2013 (Box 5)
  - Audit Support Schedules and 1978 Audit (Box 6)
  - Audit Working Papers and 1979 Audit (Box 6)
  - Audit 1980 Closing Workpapers and Account Analyses (Box 6)
  - Audit Package 1981 (Box 6)
  - Audit Reports, 1990-1994 (Box 6)
  - Audit Financial Reports, 1977-1984 (Box 6)
  - Internal Budget reports, 1995-1997 (Box 6)
  - Direct Mail Archive: 1999-2009 letters, quizzes, donation forms (Box 7)
  - Direct Mail Archive: 2010-2013 letters, quizzes, donation forms (Box 7)
  - AGI 1984 Audit (Box 7)
  - Auditors Report A133, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Auditors Report A133, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Auditors Report A133, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Financial Statements w/ independent aditor's report, 1991-1994 (Box 7)
  - Audited Financials, 2010-2012 (Box 7)
  - AGI 1982 audit package (Box 7)
  - AGI 1983 audit package (Box 7)
  - AGI 1986 summary report/ audit package (Box 7)
  - AGI 1985 audit package (Box 7)
  - AGI 1987 audit report package (Box 7)
  - AGI financial reports, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Functional expenses, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Endowment documents, undated (Box 7)
  - 1023 Application, 1977 (Box 7)
  - AGI Certificates of Incorporation, 1977 (Box 7)
  - NY Comm Trust Investment Options, 1988-1990 (Box 8)
  - AGI Affirmative Action: policy statement, media recs, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Communications Expansion, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Grant for Improving W. Mass information infrastructure involvement, 1995 (Box 8)
  - AGI Staff benefits info: surveys, reports, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Nonprofit coordinating committee, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Small Business/for-profit corporation addition to AGI comtemplation, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Washington Memo: family planning under Title IV, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Branding: organization identity, image strategies, name change, 2004 (Box 8)
  - Richard Lincoln Senior Vice President: photos, retirement letters, 1988 (Box 8)
  - USAID Funding Information, Memos, writings etc., 1979-1983 (Box 8)
  - International Family Planning Persepctives (IFPP) Mellon grants, press releases, 1987 (Box 8)
  - IFPP Budget, correspondence, subcontract information and general communications expenses, 1993-1998 (Box 8)
  - IFPP History: correspondences, funding, reader surveys, AID evaluation, 1983-1992 (Box 8)
  - IFPP Digest and Press Releases, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - AGI Annual Report 1991-1992: factsheets, charts, brochure, history, mission, committees, meetings etc (Box 9)
  - Historical Documents and Workbook Committee Senate Hearings, 1960-1970 (Box 9)
  - AGI Contraceptive Involvement/ consultation Nonoxynol-9 and Trojan, 2004-2007 (Box 9)
  - Condom Ads and TV AGI Involvement as a Resource, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Kaiser Briefing AGI Involvement, 1999-2002 (Box 9)
  - Contraceptive Effectiveness Internal Meeting Info, 2005 (Box 9)
  - AGI Improving Contraceptive Use 155/122 Media Briefing, 2008 (Box 9)
  - Identifying Service Charges to Improve Contraceptive Use Panel, 2007 (Box 9)
  - BARR Laboratories Consultation Oral CP, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Implanon Consultation (progestin implant), 2004 (Box 9)
  - AGI "Great Debate" Briefing: condoms & barrier BC, FDA labelling, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Community Informed Research in California Project: interviews on, 2008 (Box 9)
  - Santelli Teen Pregnancy Declines: abstinence programs, 2004 (Box 9)
  - NSFG: survey of family growth, teen sexual behavior/health risks, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Mathematica Evaluation: effectiveness of abstinence only education, undated (Box 9)
  - Weldon Amendment: federal refusal law on abortion & referrals, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Pharmacist Refusal Conference, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Communicating Research: A Guttmacher Institute Training for, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Association for Reproductive Health Professionals Conference, 2007 (Box 9)
  - "The Values Project", undated (Box 9)
  - IBIS Fellows Training, 2007 (Box 9)
  - NOAPP Conference: teen pregnancy prevention, evidence-based progs, 2003-2004 (Box 9)
  - Packard State Abortion Project: state abortion restrictions, 2005 (Box 9)
  - LA Roundtable(011): CA policies, teen pregnancy rates, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Chicago Roundtable (011): state-level data on access, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Orlando Roundtable (011): FL youth repro health, parental notification, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Denver Roundtable (011) comprehensive sex education, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Phoenix Roundtable (011) AZ policies, teen pregnancy prevention, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Springfield Roundtable (011) minors' access in IL, parental consent, 2005 (Box 9)
  - North Carolina Roundtable (011) research in advocacy, access for, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Maine Roundtable (011) Medicaid/public funding, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Algonquin Roundtable (011) media, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Goldman TGR Media, 2002-2003 (Box 9)
  - Project Plans: In the Know 238: grant proposals, invoices, mkting plan, 2006 (Box 9)
  - State Rankings Merck 122: release program media kit plans, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Unmet Need Worldwide 204: briefing/outreach on project, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Contraceptive Failure: factsheet article, promotion plans for data, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Abortion Worldwide 201: outreach/messaging, global trends, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Sex Ed OSI: grant proposal for evidence-based research, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Sex Education & Teens Ford 208/209: communications on sex ed, undated (Box 9)
  - PRCH Collaboration (Adolescent Reproductive Health Education Project Curriculum): GA teen education program, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Parental Involvement Contraception Casey 122, 2005-2006 (Box 9)
  - Securing Abortion Rights (118), undated (Box 9)
  - Repeat Abortion Hewlett 122, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Roe v. Wade Strategy, undated (Box 9)
  - KFF Abortion Briefing, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Kaiser AGI Involvement, 2002 (Box 9)
  - UNC STI Collaboration, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Communications Activities, undated (Box 9)
  - Innagural 2007 Information (Box 9)
  - International Family Planning Perspectives Funding, 2007 (Box 10)
  - INFO (Information and Knowledge for Optimal Health) Project Evaluation, 2007 (Box 10)
  - Johns Hopkins University INFO Proposal, 2004 (Box 10)
  - IFPP Subcontracts, undated (Box 10)
  - IFPP AID Decisions, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Communications with PIP at Jonhs Hopkins Uni, 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - IFPP Reader survey, 1991-1998 (Box 10)
  - AGI History, undated (Box 10)
  - Francophonie, 2004 (Box 10)
  - IFPP Reader Survey, 1998 (Box 10)
  - IFPP Reader Survey, 2000 (Box 10)
  - IFPP Reader Survey, 2003 (Box 10)
  - IFPP Reader Survey, 1991 (Box 10)
  - IFPP Reader Survery, 1987 (Box 10)
  - Burgess Evaluation, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Contingency Planning, 2005 (Box 10)
  - Blackwell/Creative Commons, 2007 (Box 10)
  - USAID budget discussions, 2004 (Box 10)
  - IFPP workplans, 2003-2008 (Box 10)
  - USAID meetings, 2006 (Box 10)
  - JHU Subcontracts, undated (Box 10)
  - AID's LPA Approval, 1995 (Box 10)
  - FPP and IFPP, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Sample Style Guide, 1997 (Box 10)
  - Sample Style Guide (Sheet), 2012 (Box 10)
  - In Brief Layout Guide, 2012 (Box 10)
  - IFPP EAC Dec 2000 Mtg (Box 10)
  - 2010 and 2005 EAC Meeting Info, undated (Box 10)
  - IFPP Abortion, 2003 (Box 10)
  - AID JHU Funding, 1995 (Box 10)
  - AID JHU Funding1994 Contract (Box 10)
  - AID JHU Copy Control, 1994 (Box 10)
  - FPP Evaluation, 2001 (Box 11)
  - FPP Evaluation 1990 Final Report (Box 11)
  - Journal Evaluations, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Assessment of Journal Operations, 2000-2001 (Box 11)
  - Editorial Advisory Committee, 2005-2010 (Box 11)
  - FPP Final Report, 2001 (Box 11)
  - EAC Meeting, 2006 (Box 11)
  - Family Planning Perspectives Abstract ChangeMemo from JJ, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Family Planning Perspectives Cumulative Indices 1969-1998, undated (Box 11)
  - Getting Published Workshop Donovan and Althaus, 2011 (Box 11)
  - Readings (compiled reports on a particular subject), 1973-2003 (Box 11)
  - Areal Analysis Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - Areal Analysis Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - NICHD (Determinants of Adolescent Fertility) Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 11)
  - NICHD Codebook, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - NICD Teen Statistical Analysis Unit (SAU), undated (Box 11)
  - NICHD Comments by Consultants, undated (Box 11)
  - NICHD Unobserrved Variable Adolescent Childbearing, undated (Box 11)
  - NICHD Progress and Summary Reports, undated (Box 11)
  - NICHD Final Report, undated (Box 11)
  - NICHD Business and Tech Proposals, undated (Box 11)
  - NICHD Adolescent and Childbearing Contract Teen Pregnancy Determinant, undated (Box 11)
  - Euroteen: American Life Lobby "Expsoed" by Robert Marshall, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Euroteen: "A Critical Review of 'Teenage Pregnancy in Developed Countries: Determinants and Policy Implications'" American Life Lobby by Robert J Marshall, 1982-1985 (Box 12)
  - Euroteen: American Life Lobby re: Euroteen study, undated (Box 12)
  - Euroteen: Ford Foundation Report, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Infertility Study Final Report, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - AGI Report on Infertility Services DHHS 1985 (Box 12)
  - Infertility Fielding, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Infertility Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Infertility Background Minorities, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Infertility Study Grant Proposal, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Infertility Study Conference Paper Presentation, undated (Box 12)
  - Infertility Study Interim Report, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Doctor's/Private Physician Survey, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Doctor's/Private Physician Survey Memo's and Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Doctor's Survey final report on phone and mail follow-ups, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Doctor Survey Presentation at APPP, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Doctor's Survey Correspondence, undated (Box 12)
  - Doctor's Survey Telephone Protocol, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Doctor's Survey Interview Training Guide, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Doctor's Survey Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Doctor's Survey 1982-1983 Questionnaires and Cover Letters (Box 12)
  - Doctor's Survey Methodology and Sample, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Rockefeller Surveys, undated (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller final Grant Application, undated (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller "Evaluation of the Family Planning Program: Factors Related to Serving Adolescents", 1982 (Box 13)
  - Final Report to Rockefeller for State Study, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller State Study Meeting Notes, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller State Study Correspondence, undated (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller State Study and Teens Pharmacy Survey, 1980-1986 (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller Projects Concerning Adolescent Pregnancy Proposals, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Weed and Olsen Correspondence, Report, Memo and Article Copy, 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller State Study APHA Presentation, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller State Study Physician Survey and Data, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller State Study Article Interstate Analysis, undated (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller Correspondence, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller State Study Article Drafts, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller Patient Survey Training and Coding, undated (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller "Evaluation of the Family Planning Program: Factors Related to Serving Adolescents" Sample Clinics, undated (Box 13)
  - Occasional Reports & Guttmacher Papers (the successor to Occasional Reports), 2001- 2012 (Box 13)
  - Occasional Reports & Guttmacher Papers (the successor to Occasional Reports), 2001- 2012 (Box 14)
  - International Family Planning Perspectives Multilingual 1978-2013 (Gap from 2003- 2008 b/c of funding) [Spanish] (Box 14)
  - In Brief and Facts, 1991-2013 (Box 14)
  - Contraception Counts, 1998-1999 (Box 15)
  - Issues in Brief (Policy), 1981-2005 (Box 15)
  - Historical Documents and Committee Workbook Senate Hearings, 1960-1970 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports (w/o 1982, 1977, 1978, 1979, 1985, 1994,1995), undated (Box 15)